{"1": {"question": "What is the genre of O mistress mine?", "correct": "20th Century English Art Song", "incorrect": ["20th Century Leider", "Pop", "19th Century Lieder", "19th Century English Art Song", "Jazz"]}, "2": {"question": "What does 'Allegretto amabile' mean?", "correct": "Moderately fast, and amiable (pleasant or charming)", "incorrect": ["Really fast and amiable", "Slow", "Play moderately fast on every second bar", "Quickly increase volume", "Quickly drop in Volume"]}, "3": {"question": "What does 'sempre staccato' mean?", "correct": "Always detached", "incorrect": ["Very detached", "Suddenly detached", "Always stuck", "Moderately detached", "Detachted every second note"]}, "4": {"question": "What is the form of O Mistress Mine, by Finzi?", "correct": "Modified Strophic Form", "incorrect": ["Rondo form", "Strophic Form", "Ternary form", "Through composed form", "Binary Form"]}, "5": {"question": "Which keys are used in O mistress mine?", "correct": "Eb Major and Eb Minor", "incorrect": ["G Major only", "E Major and E minor", "D Major and A major ", "C Major and G Minor", "F Major and F Minor"]}, "6": {"question": "What does 'rinforzando subito' mean?", "correct": "Sudddenly reinforce or emphasise", "incorrect": ["Suddenly get louder", "Suddenly get louder, then gradually get softer.", "Suddenly get softer", "Suddenly increase tempo", "Immediately become more gentle"]}, "7": {"question": "How many sections are there in O mistress mine?", "correct": "5", "incorrect": ["7", "4", "6", "9", "2"]}, "8": {"question": "What is the order of the sections in O mistress mine?", "correct": "The introduction, Stanza 1, Interlude, Stanza 2, Postlude.", "incorrect": ["Introduction, Stanza 1, Interlude and Stanza 2.", "Stanza 1, Stanza 2 and Postlude", "Introduction, Stanza 1 and Stanza 2", "Introduction, Stanza 1 and Postlude", "Stanza 1 and Stanza 2"]}, "9": {"question": "In O mistress mine, what is the mood/feeling of the major key sections?", "correct": "Bright and Jaunty", "incorrect": ["Sad and lonely", "Depressing", "Meh", "Calm", "Quick and Uptight"]}, "10": {"question": "What is the underlying message of the song?", "correct": "To seize life's joys and pleasures while you can", "incorrect": ["Only do what you want to do.", "Expect to have unfortunate things in your life.", "There is no message", "Stay on your phone the whole day", "Work hard you will be rewarded"]}, "11": {"question": "Who wrote the source material that Finzi used for O Mistress Mine?", "correct": "William Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Wilhelm M\u00c3\u00bcller", "Michael", "George Handel", "Wilhelm Shakespeare", "Gerald Finzi"]}, "12": {"question": "Which sections in O mistress mine change to Eb Minor?", "correct": "Stanza 1 and Stanza 2", "incorrect": ["Introduction, Interlude and Postlude", "Only the Introduction", "Interlude and Postlude", "Introduction and Postlude ", "None"]}, "13": {"question": "What movement # is O Mistress Mine (within the larger work it is a part of)?\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "correct": "Fourth", "incorrect": ["Fifth", "First", "Second", "Not Part of a larger work at all", "Third"]}, "14": {"question": "What larger work is O Mistress Mine from?\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t", "correct": "Let us Garlands Bring", "incorrect": ["Winterreise", "Songs of Travel", "Liederkreis", "Dichterliebe", "Die sch\u00c3\u00b6ne M\u00c3\u00bcllerin"]}, "15": {"question": "What type of work is the larger work that O Mistress Mine is from?", "correct": "Art Song", "incorrect": ["Lieder", "Opera", "Folk Music", "Blues", "Country Music"]}, "16": {"question": "What play is the lyrics for O Mistress Mine from?", "correct": "Twelfth Night", "incorrect": ["Macbeth", "Romeo and Juliet", "Othello", "Midsummer Night's Dream", "King Lear"]}, "17": {"question": "What is the rhyme scheme for each stanza in O mistress mine?", "correct": "aabccb", "incorrect": ["abac", "aba", "ab", "aabbccaa", "abca"]}, "18": {"question": "What is the instrumentation for O Mistress mine?", "correct": "Voice and piano", "incorrect": ["Typical String Quartet - 2 Violins, a Viola and a Cello", "2 Violins", "Violin and Piano", "Trumpet and Piano", "Piano only"]}, "19": {"question": "What dynamic does O mistress mine begin on?", "correct": "mf", "incorrect": ["f ", "p", "a bit louder than mp", "fff", "There is no dynamic marking"]}, "20": {"question": "What is the name of a six-line stanza?", "correct": "sextain", "incorrect": ["sixtain", "six-line stanza", "sextillion", "quintain", "septet"]}, "21": {"question": "What is the cause of the presence of Cb, Db and Gb in O mistress mine?", "correct": "Modal Mixture", "incorrect": ["An unintended mistake by Finzi", "The notes used to be part of the key O mistress mine uses but then was changed", "A key change in the piece", "Some person sabotaged the sheet music and added flats randomly", "It was a trend at the time to add random notes to compositions"]}, "22": {"question": "What type of articulation is used to play the left hand in O mistress Mine?", "correct": "Staccato", "incorrect": ["Accents", "Tenutos", "Legato", "marcatos", "staccatissimo"]}, "23": {"question": "What does 'A Tempo' mean?", "correct": "Return to original speed", "incorrect": ["Literally just means \"A tempo\"", "Play a random tempo", "Gradually slow down and come to a stop", "Stay at the current tempo", "Play freely and ignore all past tempo markings"]}, "24": {"question": "What does senza rall mean?", "correct": "Without slowing down", "incorrect": ["Sneeze roll", "Slowly deacrease in dynamic", "slowly deacrease in tempo", "Without speeding up", "Gently and Gradually slow down "]}, "25": {"question": "What does 'lunga' mean?", "correct": "Long pause", "incorrect": ["Long phrasing", "Get down and do 10 Lunges!", "Lower your dynamic level", "Return to original speed slowly", "An alternate spelling of \"longer\""]}, "26": {"question": "When was 'Let us garlands bring' composed?", "correct": "1942", "incorrect": ["1952", "1924", "1842", "2023", "1130"]}, "27": {"question": "How many song cycles did Finzi compose?", "correct": "At least 8", "incorrect": ["12", "He didn't compose any song cycles -  he disliked them very much.", "9", "18", "4"]}, "28": {"question": "When did English art songs start to emerge?", "correct": "The late sixteenth century", "incorrect": ["2nd century", "100 BCE", "1700's", "1892", "Unknown", "The late 1600s"]}, "29": {"question": "Who composed the instrumentation to O mistress mine?", "correct": "Gerald Finzi", "incorrect": ["William Shakespeare", "Mozart", "Schubert", "Wilhelm M\u00c3\u00bcller", "Beethoven"]}, "30": {"question": "What does 'Molto' mean?", "correct": "much, very", "incorrect": ["Molten Rock", "Translates to \"Motor\" - Gradually Speed up", "Play very gently", "Play as loudly as you think is necessary", "Extremely soft "]}, "31": {"question": "What does 'Cantabile' mean?", "correct": "In a singing matter", "incorrect": ["much, very", "In a sad tone", "Without Slowing down", "It is the marking for a new stanza", "Freely"]}, "32": {"question": "In Shakespeare's Twelfth Night, who sings O mistress mine?", "correct": "Feste, a clown.", "incorrect": ["Malvolio", "Duke Orsino", "Maria", "No one does - the script writer couldn't decide", "Fabian"]}, "33": {"question": "What does 'Modal Mixture' mean?", "correct": "the use of chords belonging to a parallel key", "incorrect": ["The Mixture of Time Signatures", "the use of random tempos", "experiment with a variety of keys", "The adding of tone to a piece", "A variety of note lengths"]}, "34": {"question": "When was the \"English musical Renaissance\"?", "correct": "1890-1900", "incorrect": ["1790-1800", "1990-2000", "2190-2200", "Porridge", "It actually never happened"]}, "35": {"question": "What was the English art song increasingly dominated by during its development?", "correct": "The German lied", "incorrect": ["The war that was occuring at the time", "Emerging musicians who had no idea how to compose art song", "ACDC", "Irish folk songs", "Jazz"]}, "36": {"question": "What led to the 'English musical Renaissance'", "correct": "The folk-song revival movement", "incorrect": ["Finzi's creativity", "The first ever Rock and Roll record", "The first German Lied", "The first record company", "The end of ragtime music"]}, "37": {"question": "Ralf Vaughn Williams, John Ireland and Arnold Bax were all what?", "correct": "Significant English composers of the twentieth century", "incorrect": ["Minor English composers of the twentieth century", "Significant composers of lied", "Significant poets of the twentieth century", "Significant English composers of the nineteenth century", "German people"]}, "38": {"question": "When in Shakespeare's play Twelfth Night is O mistress mine sung?", "correct": "Act 2, Scene 3", "incorrect": ["Act 3, Scene 2", "Act 2, Scene 2", "Act 6, Scene 4", "Act 2, Scene 4", "At the end"]}, "39": {"question": "Footpath and Stile was Finzi's first song cycle, but what was Let us garlands bring?", "correct": "Finzi's third last", "incorrect": ["Finzi's thirteenth", "Shakespeares' last", "Schubert's third last", "Finzi's second last", "Finzi's Last"]}, "40": {"question": "Finzi's compositional efforts were particularly centred on what?", "correct": "Vocal music", "incorrect": ["tenor clef", "Piano Accompaniment", "String music", "Rock Music", "String Quartets"]}, "41": {"question": "The end of each stanza, the cadence leads into what?", "correct": "The next piano section", "incorrect": ["A short instrumental break", "The next stanza"]}, "42": {"question": "What happens in the final two lines in each stanza?", "correct": "A change of mood", "incorrect": []}, "43": {"question": "Between which years was Finzi alive?", "correct": "1901 - 1956", "incorrect": []}, "44": {"question": "What genre is Twelfth Night?", "correct": "Comedy", "incorrect": []}, "45": {"question": "What do the beginning and ending of each section in O Mistress Mine have in common?", "correct": "Similar music", "incorrect": []}, "46": {"question": "What does ritard. poco mean?", "correct": "Gradually slow down a little", "incorrect": []}, "47": {"question": "What is the given tempo marking for O Mistress Mine?", "correct": "Allegretto amabile", "incorrect": []}, "48": {"question": "What is the precise tempo marked for O Mistress Mine on the score?", "correct": "Minim = about 84 bpm", "incorrect": []}, "49": {"question": "Which sections in O Mistress mine have a time signature change?", "correct": "Stanza 1 and 2", "incorrect": []}, "50": {"question": "What time signature(s) does O Mistress Mine use?", "correct": "2/2 and 3/2", "incorrect": []}, "51": {"question": "What is a song cycle?", "correct": "A set of songs composed to be played in a certain sequence", "incorrect": []}, "52": {"question": "How many seperate texts by Shakespeare are used in Let us Garlands Bring?", "correct": "5", "incorrect": []}, "53": {"question": "What was one of the most common things between Art Song Composers?", "correct": "They turned to putting their music to important English Poets' text", "incorrect": []}, "54": {"question": "Shakespeare, Milton, Wordsworth, Coleridge and Hardy are all what?", "correct": "Important English Poets", "incorrect": []}, "55": {"question": "What is 5-1?", "correct": "4", "incorrect": ["(please replace this question, I'm just making it 55)"]}}